<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Kerem Yıldırır</title>
        <link>/</link>
        <description>Latest blog posts from Kerem Yıldırır</description>

        
        <language>en-us</language>
        

        

        

        

        
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 16:16:24 +0200</lastBuildDate>
        

        
        <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        

        
            
        <item>
          <title>Divergence-Free Shape Correspondence with Time Dependent Vector Fields</title>
          <link>/projects/idp/</link>
          <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/projects/idp/</guid>
          <description>IDP [TODO] funky videos of intermediate results</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>Multiple Object Tracking with Tracktor</title>
          <link>/projects/mot/</link>
          <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 16:09:23 +0200</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/projects/mot/</guid>
          <description>Multiple Object Tracking Challenge by TUM. Implemented vanilla Tracktor with Faster R-CNN and basic motion and reidentificaiton model. [TODO] video and source code</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>3D Instance Segmentation</title>
          <link>/projects/3d-segmentation/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 23:30:14 +0200</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/projects/3d-segmentation/</guid>
          <description>Autonomous Driving Praktikum 3D Instance Segmentation of the point cloud using 2D detections provided from Mask R-CNN Does not require any annotated 3D data! Original implementation is not suitable for real time due to slow inference speed of Mask R-CNN
2D detections   [TODO] LDLS picture
We solve the performance issue of LDLS by swapping Mask R-CNN with YOLACT, a faster instance segmentation model. For any given image and LiDAR data pair, we first perform 2D Instance Object Segmentation using YOLACT We then apply LDLS to label the point cloud data with the detected classes in 2D.</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>One Table to Count Them All: Parallel Frequency Estimation on Single-Board Computers</title>
          <link>/projects/sketch/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 23:30:14 +0200</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/projects/sketch/</guid>
          <description>Id Modi Id modi explicabo non accusantium accusantium. Voluptates laborum est exercitationem odit voluptate dicta laborum nemo. Dolorum et aliquam qui dolorem voluptates ducimus voluptatibus. Quia sunt molestiae id ut. Necessitatibus itaque sed unde sit repellendus sit. Error pariatur deserunt dignissimos saepe cupiditate beatae.
Nemo animi
Illum quae laudantium quia vel facere aliquid earum. Inventore culpa perspiciatis et veniam et amet distinctio. Facilis expedita doloremque voluptates nihil et sint commodi et.</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>Plant  Identification with Deep Learning Ensembles</title>
          <link>/projects/plant_id/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 23:21:09 +0200</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/projects/plant_id/</guid>
          <description>Tempora Maxime Illo quod est aut aperiam ullam. Eum aliquam vel velit hic dolores sunt molestiae saepe. Est et cupiditate est saepe.
Qui quo beatae minima. Tempora maxime facere praesentium officiis maiores quia. Quia placeat nihil sint aperiam autem quia recusandae et. In quas nulla cum fuga. Dolores voluptas quia facere atque omnis rerum corrupti repellendus.
Facere quod Voluptatibus neque iure aut doloremque excepturi. Quidem aut unde magni. Harum qui molestiae ut itaque labore voluptas.</description>
        </item>
            
        <item>
          <title>Plant Disease Identification</title>
          <link>/projects/plant_disease/</link>
          <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 23:21:09 +0200</pubDate>
          
          <guid>/projects/plant_disease/</guid>
          <description>Tempora Maxime Illo quod est aut aperiam ullam. Eum aliquam vel velit hic dolores sunt molestiae saepe. Est et cupiditate est saepe.
Qui quo beatae minima. Tempora maxime facere praesentium officiis maiores quia. Quia placeat nihil sint aperiam autem quia recusandae et. In quas nulla cum fuga. Dolores voluptas quia facere atque omnis rerum corrupti repellendus.
Facere quod Voluptatibus neque iure aut doloremque excepturi. Quidem aut unde magni. Harum qui molestiae ut itaque labore voluptas.</description>
        </item>
            
        
    </channel>
</rss>
